DHRUV JAWALKAR

https://in.linkedin.com/in/dhruv-jawalkar-43b8816b

Email: dhruv.jawalkar@gmail.com

Phone: +1 (510) 399-3469

SUMMARY:

Pursuing a master's degree in Computer Science at Oregon State University. Have 4 years of experience in product development, including a Silicon Valley startup. Have built and delivered web applications to clients. Currently pursuing my interest in Deep Learning technologies applied in the field of Computer Vision during my master's program. https://github.com/DhruvJawalkar

EDUCATION:

Oregon State University, USA

Sept 2018

GPA: -

M.S in Computer Science

BITS-Pilani, India Jul 2013

Bachelor in Engineering Honors in Computer Science GPA: 6.79 / 10

WORK EXPERIENCE:

Senior Software Development Engineer

Dec 2016 - Jun 2017 (7 month)

Kony Labs, India

• Part of MBaaS (Mobile Backend as a Service) console team, was hired and responsible for improving console performance and user experience.

Software Development Engineer

Apr 2016 - Dec 2016 (9 months)

Engage BDR, India

 Lead front-end development for upcoming product ICONICREACH, platform to connect brand advertisers to Instagram celebrity influencers.

UI Engineer Aug 2013 - Apr 2016 (2.5 yrs)

Fission Computer Labs, India

- Built web apps for silicon valley Ad-Tech startup, DeepForestMedia
- Developed their Ad campaign management portal, DSP.
- Developed campaign performance monitoring dashboard, which helped customers make effective business decisions.

TECHNICAL SKILLS:

Programming languages: Python, JavaScript, Bash

ML Stack: PyTorch, NumPy, Pandas, Scikit-Learn, Jupyter Notebook

Web Technologies: Angular JS, Grunt JS

Software and tools: Git, Visual Studio, WebStorm

Machine Learning and Deep Learning Projects:

- Object Detection Implemented a model to classify and localize objects in an image, using PyTorch, PASCAL dataset
- Multi Class Classification Implemented a model to categories all objects given an image
- Clustering Implemented Fuzzy Clustering (soft clustering) on datasets, to identify best possible clustering